Guide to the New York State College of Home Economics Office of the Registrar records, 1915-1965.
New York State College of Home Economics Office of the Registrar records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
New York State College of Home Economics Office of the Registrar records, 1915-1965.
23-11-2701
New York State College of Home Economics.Office of the Registrar.
1.1 c.f.
Printed Materials, Photographs
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Graduate student photographs and career information.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Graduate student photographs and career information.
SUBJECTS
Names:
New York State College of Home Economics.; Cornell University--Students.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
During student's lifetime individual student records restricted to permission of student and office of origin.
CONTAINER LIST
- Contains career information and photographs for the following graduate students in the New York State College of Home Economics
  - Helen Abell MS and PhD, 1947, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Helen Helen Adams/Davis MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jocelyn Adams/Bernholdt MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ruth Ahnert/Foster MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jean Aitchinson/Atkins MS - photo only, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Elizabeth Albertse MS, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Vera Alderson/McCready MS - photo only, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Evelyn Aldridge/Mason MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Annette Allison/Vincent MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Phyllis Altman/Leeking MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Altpeter/Nordquist MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Hekmat El-Sayed Aly/Dakroury PhD, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Paul Ammon PhD, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marjery Andersen/Einstein MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Doris Anderson MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Joana Appiah MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Sadye Appleby/Young MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dorothy Arate MS and PhD, 1950, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mary Arendas MA, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Patricia Arkinstall MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Ignacio Armillas MA, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Helen Armstrong/Kubacky MS and PhD, 1957, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marjorie Armstrong MA, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Carolyn Arnold MS, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Barbara Atherton/Case MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Jeanne Galloway Atwell MA, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Marlene Devilbiss Averitte MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Rachel Avishar MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Mildred Babcock MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Suzanne Bratton Badenhop (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Betty White Bailey PhD, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Louise Bailey, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Betty Bain/Bowman MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Joanne Baker/Lavery MS - photo only, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Baldi MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Erna Bamford/Breton MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jerry Banks MS - photo only, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Judith Banton MS - photo only, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jeanne Baranek MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barbara Barber/Kennedy MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barbara Barnes/McDonald MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth Bastian/Chepus MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jessie Bateman PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Margaret Westbrook Bates MNS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Judith Baumler/Reynolds MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Molly Beall/Bullard MS - photo only, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elizabeth Bechtel (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ruth Neptune Beckwith MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Shirley Beckwith/Jaslo MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nicole Begin MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Catherine Behnke/Burke MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Betty Bell Prov. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Helen Bell MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Virginia Bell - photo only (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Torres Bellavista MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gladys Bellinger MS and PhD, 1948, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bernice Belshaw MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Phyllis Berger/Hemmer MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Sushill Bhalla (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Helen Bickel MS - photo only, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Suzanne Bratton Badenhop (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mary Billings/Orsenigo MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ezelle Birchette, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Myra Bishop PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dorothy Bissell MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rachel Sanders Bizal MS and PhD, 1929, 1933 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Helen Bjorklund MS - photo only, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gladys Black MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gertrude Blaker MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Abraham Blum PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Jeanne Moscowitz Blum MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Helen Boettcher/Forshang MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Barbara Bond/Toliver MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ruth Bones MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Bernice Borgman PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constance Bourdeau MNS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Susan Bowers (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Ann Brady/Dwelly (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Henry Brandt PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mary Braseth/Engebretson (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Rosanne Braun/Schlussel (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Laure Brigham/Stier MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constance Brine/Jordan PhD - photo only, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Joan Broadcorens MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lois Brockman PhD - photo only, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Carlfred Broderick PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Gladys Brown MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Nerissa Brown MA (Ed), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Kathleen Browne/Ittig MS and PhD, 1973, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Dorothy Brownsfield PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Lillian Buckingham/Abernathy MS (Ed), 1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Isabelle Bull MS (Ed), 1935 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Constance Burgess MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Edith Burke MS, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Louise Burnette MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Elaine Burns MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Hedda Burstein Prov. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Mary McDorman Burton PhD, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Edna Busekist MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Eleanor Byer MAT, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Marjorie Caldwell MS - photo only, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Esperanza Callao MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ada Marie Campbell PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Louise Campbell MS, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Florence Campbell/Phelps MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Muriel Campbell Prov. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Pearl Posey Campbell PhD, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mary Agnes Carlin MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Constance Carlson/Metcalf MS - photo only, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Gay Carnes (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Carpenter MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Helen Carroll MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Marian Case MS (Ed), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Georgeanna Cass (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Paulette Cassen/Mulvaney MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Geraldine Catanzaro MA, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Florence Chan/Appoldt MS - photo only, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mew Lan Chee MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Helen Chen/Chung MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dorothy Chuan/Lee MS - photo only, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Evangeline Chung MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mildred Church/Hoar MA, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - DeLene Clark/Holbrook MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Sara Jane Clark/Ball MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - F. June Clark MS and Ed, 1946, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Janet Clay MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Judith Cobb MA, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mary Cockefair/Holt MS - photo only, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Rodney Cocking PhD, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Florence Coe/King MS (Ed), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Colburn/Tigner MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mary Colgrove MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Marta Coll-Camalez MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Alice Collings MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Betty Collins/Carl MS, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Patricia Collins MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Susanna Colton/Arnold MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dolores Comeaux/Brogan MS and PhD, 1950, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Doris Conklin/Logan MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mary Connaughton MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Kita Connelly MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Mabel Conway MS, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ruth Cook PhD, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Genevieve Coon (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Stanley Coopersmith PhD, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Amy Corlies (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Correll MS - photo only, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lilla Cortright/Halchin MS (Ed), 1943 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Dorothy Cousens MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Anne Coveney PhD, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Nancy Cox/Myers MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Edith Crammatte MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Bernice Crawford (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Martha Crawford MS - photo only, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Elsie Crouthamel/Bassett MA, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Jane Crow PhD, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Marcia Crum/Hackett MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - AManda Cummings MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Lala Curry MS, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Virginia Cutler PhD, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Janina Czajkowski MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Ruth Dales PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Claire Daime MNS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Theodore Darby PhD, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Lillian Davenport/Jones MS- photo only, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mildred Davis/Schlater PhD, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Euphemia Deade/Bouroughs MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Fannie Metcalf Degroat PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Katherine Delany MNS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Margaret Delany MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Vladimir DeLissovoy PhD, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Susan Delony MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Kathryn Denniston (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Gladys Derby/Falconer MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Marilyn Derby/Crary MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mary Dever/Souther/Copp MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Elizabeth Diao/Huan PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Nancy Dickerson/Elliott MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Helen Diehl MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Mary Agnes Dinsmore MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Marguerite Decker Dixon MS, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Josiah Dodds PhD, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Irene Downey MS - photo only, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Carolyn Driver MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Rachel Dube/Pilon MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Charlotte Duncan/Russell MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Joan Durland/Bur MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Helen Dzwonczyk/Tunison MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Dorothy Eastman/Porter MS (Ed), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mary Francis Eaton (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Gabrielle Edelman/Marchbanks MA, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - James Edmondson MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Owen Edwards MS, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marguerite Edwards MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Premala Edwards/Brewster PhD - photo only, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mary Egan MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marianne Eger (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth Elbert MS and PhD, 1951, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Jean Elkind MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Marcella Ellett MS- photo only, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Joan Ellison MNS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Elizabeth Empey PhD, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Ann Erickson/Henderson MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Myrtle Ericson (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Katherine Devanna Evans PhD, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Nannie Evans MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Fay Fagan MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Irene Fagin (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ann Fahnestock MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Helen Farmer MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mona Fawcett (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alice Featherstone/Caldwell MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Gail Felcyn/Thompson MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Nancy Fendall/Emerson MA, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ruth Fenton/Bascom MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Virginia Ferguson MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Janet Fietsam/Hale MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Florence Finger - photo only (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Bliss Finlayson/Ream MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ermina Fisher MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Patricia Fitzgerald/Moothart MS, 196 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - George Fitzelle PhD - photo only, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Clarel Flanders/Embree MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Margaret Florea/McKennon MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alice Follender/Harris MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Rebecca Folsom/Ferguson MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marie Folson/Clark MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Mary Foo/Lee MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Anne Ford/Geis MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Marlene Forde/Kehler MS - photo only, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lois Foreman/Spangler MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Portis Billings Foster MA, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Jean Francis/Apgar MS and PhD, 1959, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Ellen Frazier/Picinich MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Lucille Frech/Coultrap MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Doris Fredd/Sanders MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Edith Freeman/Polkinghorne PhD, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Janet Fritz MA - photo only, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Elsie Gabel/Lutz MA, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Marvel Gage/Luykx MS - photo only, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mary Osborn Gallway MA and PhD, 1954, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sylvia Gardels/Wahl MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - David Gardner PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Vera Gardner (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A. Marjorie Garland/Grantham MS (Ed), 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ruth Garette/Breden MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Janet Gaudin/Boudinet MS, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nancy Baird Gentili MS, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Bertha Gibson MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ethelwyn Gibson/Cornelius MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Isobel Gibson/Searls MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sarah Gilbert MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Althea Gillmeister/Mosher MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mabel Gladin/Rogers MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nancy Glenn/Hansen MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Susie Golding/Langley MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Nyla Gorham MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ruth Gosser/Ipe (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Regina Gottlieb MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Judith Gould/Bridge MA - photo only, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Melvina Godwa MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Charlan Graff MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Aglaea Grammen/Stoycos MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Ruth Grant Menten (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth Grawemeyer/Cassel MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Mary Green PhD, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Betty Greer/Waldner MNS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Joyce Griffin/Lovell MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Olive Griffin/Carpenter/Boehlecke MS (Ed), 1947 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Neil Grim (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Elizabeth Gruginskis (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Audrey Guthrie MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Julie Haines/Reddin MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Joanne Hammonds/McDonald MS - photo, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Aaren Hansen/Freeberg MS - photo only, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mary Hansuld/Moore MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Charlene Harding (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annanelle Hardt MA, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sarah Harper (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Inez Kemble Harrill PhD, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Grace Fowlder Harrison MA, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Kathryn Harrison/Madsen (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jane Hart/Curvey MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mabel Hastie MS, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mary Hasty/Greeg MS (Ed), 1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Dorothy Hatch/Kragt MS, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Helen Betty Hatch/Landsberger PhD, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Sarah Hawes MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mary Hayes MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Bernadette Eileen Heagney/Stevenson MS (Ed), 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mary Healy MS (Ed), 1950 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Corinne Heaton/Staples MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jennie Heaton/Knutson MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Martha Necke (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Shirley Heinze MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Anna Heiss MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Jean Henderson (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Marrietta Henderson MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mary Henderson PhD ? (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ruth Henderson Smith MS, 1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Harriet Herbrandson MS (Ed), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Marian Hermance MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Nina Herndon/Mercer MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Mary Hersey/Ammon MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Barbara Higgins MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Ruth Highberger MS and PhD, 1944, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Carlene Hillman MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Margaret Hockin/Harrington MS and PhD, 1941, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Ruth Hodgson/Klein MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Anna Hoene/Harmuth PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Catherine Mogan MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - John Hogarty (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Dorothy Hogle (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marland Holladay PhD - photo only, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Maybell Holmes PhD, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Eleanor Holmwood MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Barbara Holt MS and PhD, 1966, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Karen Horn/Sairanen MS - photo only, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Marilyn Horn/Bohmont MS and PhD, 1947, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Valerie Horn/Gyrisco MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Priscilla Horning/Crabtree MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Virginia Howse MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Chiang-Hsiang Hsu/Chang PhD, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alice Hudson (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Francis Hugo PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Frances Humm/Fitzgerald (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Patricia Hunt MS, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Viola Hunt/Wilkinson MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Patricia Hyduk MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Rachel Ice/Hubbard MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Edith Windels Illick MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ruth Ingalis/Morrison PhD, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Hazel Ingersoll PhD, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Lanell Irvin/Smith MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Pearl Breitmaier Isenberg MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Marion Jacobson PhD, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Mariam Jameson/Harrover MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Helene Jean - photo only (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Frederica Jefferson PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Doris Allen Jennings MS (Ed), 1938 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Frances Jensen/Simons PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Wilcox Johnson MS, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ethel Johnson/Crane MS (Ed), 1944 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Jerry Johnson/Soechting MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Katherine Johnson/Karikka MS - photo only, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Marada Johnson MS, 1931 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Muriel Johnson MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Ruth Johnson (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Kathleen Johnston PhD, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Marian Joiner MNS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Alice Jones/Drew MS, 1943 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Erna Jones/Hoover PhD, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - M. Margaret Jordan (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Barbara Joy (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Florence Deyol Judy MS (Ed), 1947 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Leonards Martinez Jurado PhD, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Doris Hudson Justice MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth Kaiser MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Helen Kallenberg/Hoffman MS, 1936 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Godavari Kamalanathan MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Estelle Kane (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arthur Kaplan PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Patricia Kelley/Rowland MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Alice Kelly/Iverson MS - photo only, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Constance Kelsey MA, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Janice Madigan Kennedy MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Nancy Kern (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Elizabeth Marion Kerr MNS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mary Kesler/Lyon PhD, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lucile Ketchum MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mona Khoury/Schmitz MA, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Wadad Khoury (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Barbara Kimball/Farnham MS (Ed), 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Grace Van Loon Kimball MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bertha King (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Anne Kinsel/Wolford MS - photo only, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Mary Kirkpatrick/Dienst MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Eleanor Kling/Ensign MS - photo only, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Lorine Knight PhD, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Marjorie Knoll PhD, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Elmer Knowles PhD, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Peter Komor PhD, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Ardath Krueger/Powell MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Tsun-Hsien Kwan/Bhagata MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Pauline LaBouliere/Crowley MS - photo only, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lourdes Labrador MS, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lola Lackey/Weaver MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Dorotha Lam/Hadden MS (Ed), 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Jessie Lambden/Coles MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ruth Lamont/Juracka MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Madeleine Lanctot MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Aldene Scantlin Langford (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lillian Larson MS, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lora Larson/Brown MS - photo only, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Amalia Lautz PhD, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Sarah Lawson/Hahn MS, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Fay Bowman LeBeau MS, 1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Corinne Blum LeBovit MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Frankye Daniels Ledbetter MS, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Alberta Lee MS, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Donna Lee/Boardman (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ki Yull Lee (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Lilly Lee MA - photo only, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Viletta Leite MS, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Anita Lester MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Fern Letnes MA, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Marion Soun Lew MS - photo only, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Anna Lewis MS (Ed), 1935 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Mary Lawson Lewis MS and PhD, 1948, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Jaclin Lilienthal/Davidson (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Rachel Liner/Glovinsky MS, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Betsy Link/Kammerer MS and PhD, 1969, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Elizabeth Little MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Louise Little MS, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Nien-Chang Liu/Chang MS, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Ruth Lloyd MS (Ed), 1958 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Agnes Lodwick/Kilby MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Dorothy Lohmeyer/Rayburn MS, 1942 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Lela-Lillian Lones MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Reha Loosli MS, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Martha Lorenz (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Paulina Lorenzana/Dohllain MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Evelyn Lorenzen PhD, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Lloyd Lovell PhD, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Florence Wilkinson Low MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Mary Lowther (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Katherine Luedecke/Laird MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Eleanor Lund/Chamberlain MS, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Bonnie Lyerly/Fowler MS, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Jeannette Lynch (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Lois Lynch/Mallison MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Dorothy Lyon MS, 1944 (Box 1, Folder 12A)
  - Edith Mummery Habon - photo only (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Elizabeth Mackay (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Eva Mackin/Eaton MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ingeborg MacKellar PhD, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Victoria MacKenzie MS, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Audry Page MacLeod Prov (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Shirley Titcomb Mader (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Kathryn Madera/Miller MS, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Edith Maier/Singh MS, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Dolores Maloney MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Katherine Manchester MS, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Marilyn Manning/Hallisey MS, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Sarah Manning MS and PhD, 1949, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Chester Mapes MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Elsie Marco MS, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Ruth Marshall MS (Ed), 1953 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - May Maskow MS, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Doris Mawhinney/Palzer MS, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Lila Maxson/Richman MS, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Esther McAllester MS, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Mary McAuley/Bree MS, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 13)